Southwest Folklore Center Sound Disc Collection, 1945-1987
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Wildwood flower, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Johnny Schroeder, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Wildwood flower --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2534 (7in.)
- Fickle heart, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Bob Morris, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Fickle heart --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2535 (7in.)
- Baby face, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Earl Neff, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Baby face --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2536 (7in.)
- Blue suede shoes, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Dale Durbin, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Blue suede shoes --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2539 (7in.)
- Coon Creek party line, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Phyllis Kraft, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Coon Creek party line --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2540 (7in.)
- Tom and Jerry -- Jerry's hoedown, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys featuring Jerry Allen on banjo... Instrumental... Tom and Jerry -- Jerry's hoedown --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2542 (7in.)
- Girl with the golden hair, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Del Price, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Girl with the golden hair --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2543 (7in.)
- Cindy, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Earl Neff, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Cindy --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2544 (7in.)
- Barney Google, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Dick Manning, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Barney Google --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2545 (7in.)
- Who's sorry now, Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Earl Neff, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Who's sorry now --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2546 (7in.)
- Hazel eyes, Dukes of Mesa, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Dukes of Mesa... Dale Durbin, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Hazel eyes --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2548 (7in.)
- Divorce her C.O.D., Schroeder's Playboys, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Clarence Gowens, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Divorce her C.O.D. --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2549 (7in.)
- Ramblin' wreck, Dukes of Mesa, 1957; Phoenix, AZ., Produced by Dash Record Company; c1957, 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Music of Dukes of Mesa... Charles Lovett, caller... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance with instrumental... Ramblin' wreck --; SWF 81.3/D.(45).2550 (7in.)
- Oh baby mine -- Swanee, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Square dance with calls... Oh baby mine -- Swanee --; SWF 81.3/D.(78) (10in.)
- Aba-daba honeymoon -- My little girl, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Mike Michele, caller... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Tony Cordasco, bass... Singing square dance with calls... Aba-daba honeymoon -- My little girl --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).502 (10in.)
- Jessie polka square -- She's just right for you, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Mike Michele, caller... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Tony Cordasco, bass... Singing square dance with calls... Jessie polka square -- She's just right for you --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).503 (10in.)
- Down yonder, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Mike Michele, caller... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Tony Cordasco, bass... Singing square dance with calls and singing square dance without calls... Down yonder --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).504 (10in.)
- Tennessee polka square, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Mike Michele, caller... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Tony Cordasco, bass... Square dance with calls and square dance without calls... Tennessee polka square --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).511 (10in.)
- When you're smiling, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Mike Michele, caller... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Tony Cordasco, bass... Square dance with calls and square dance without calls... When you're smiling --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).517 (10in.)
- Chinatown my Chinatown -- Toot toot tootsie, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Mike Michele, caller... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Tony Cordasco, bass... Square dance with calls... Chinatown my Chinatown -- Toot toot tootsie --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).518 (10in.)
- Chinatown my Chinatown -- Toot toot tootsie, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Mike Michele, caller... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Tony Cordasco, bass... Square dance with calls... Chinatown my Chinatown -- Toot toot tootsie --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).518 (10in.)
- Sheik of Araby -- When you're smiling, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Mike Michele, caller... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Square dance with calls... Sheik of Araby -- When you're smiling --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).519 (10in.)
- Plaid and calico, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Mike Michele, caller... Square dance with calls and square dance without calls... Plaid and calico --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).537 (10in.)
- Lady's song, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Mike Michele, caller... Square dance with calls and square dance without calls... Lady's song/Jean's song --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).539 (10in.)
- Loose talk, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Mike Michele, caller... Square dance with calls and square dance without calls... Loose talk --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).540 (10in.)
- Rancho Grande -- San Antonio Rose, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Morris Sevada, caller... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Tony Cordasco, bass... Singing square dance with calls... Rancho Grande -- San Antonio Rose --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).550 (10in.)
- Old fashioned girl -- Red River Valley, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Orchestra and background voices by Schroeder's Playboys... Milt Paisant, caller... Square dance with calls... Old fashioned girl -- Red River Valley --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).551 (10in.)
- Trindad twister -- Wright's star, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Marvin Shilling, caller... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Tony Cordasco, bass; W. S. Garland Green, fiddle... Square dance with calls... Trindad twister -- Wright's star --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).572 (10in.)
- El Paso star -- Four gents star, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Marvin Shilling, caller... Square dance with calls... El Paso star/Cripple Creek -- Four gents star/Grey eagle --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).575 (10in.)
- Wheelbarrow -- Allemande breaks #2, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Marvin Shilling, caller... Square dance with calls... Wheelbarrow/Shaw's reels -- Allemande breaks #2/Cripple Creek --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).577 (10in.)
- Allemande breaks #3 -- Steppin' high, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Marvin Shilling, caller... Square dance with calls... Allemande breaks #3/Sally Goodin' -- Steppin' high/Old Joe Clark --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).578 (10in.)
- Swing all eight, Pancho Baird's Gitfiddlers, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Pancho Baird's Gitfiddlers... Pancho Baird, caller... Square dance with calls and square dance without calls... Swing all eight --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).588 (10in.)
- Gray Eagle -- Braying Mule, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Square dance without calls... Gray Eagle -- Braying Mule --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).610 (10in.)
- Calico polka -- Lili Marlene, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Round dance... Calico polka -- Lili Marlene --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).701 (10in.)
- Desert stomp -- Arizona waltz, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... John Schroeder, guitar; Bill Yates, piano; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Round dance... Desert stomp -- Arizona waltz --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).705 (10in.)
- Harvest moon mixer -- Beautiful Betsy, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Harvest moon mixer -- Beautiful Betsy --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).710 (10in.)
- Anytime -- Sunflower polka, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Round dance... Anytime -- Sunflower polka --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).711 (10in.)
- Southern swing -- A mighty pretty waltz, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Bill Yates, piano; Tony Cordasco, bass... Round dance... Southern swing -- A mighty pretty waltz --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).713 (10in.)
- Summertime waltz -- Kalico kicker, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Round dance... Summertime waltz -- Kalico kicker --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).715 (10in.)
- Summertime waltz -- Kalico kicker, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Round dance... Summertime waltz -- Kalico kicker --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).715 (10in.) #2
- Three o'clock waltz -- Heart o' Texas, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Round dance... Three o'clock waltz -- Heart o' Texas --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).717 (10in.)
- Three o'clock waltz -- Heart o' Texas, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Round dance... Three o'clock waltz -- Heart o' Texas --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).717 (10in.)
- Near you -- Georgia polka, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Round or mixer... Near you -- Georgia polka --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).726 (10in.)
- Truly truly fair -- Ragtime melody, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Square dance without calls... Truly truly fair -- Ragtime melody --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).804 (10in.)
- Tennessee polka square -- Hello, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Square dance without calls... Tennessee polka square -- Hello --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).805 (10in.)
- End of the world -- Sunflower square, Schroeder's Playboys, Phoenix, AZ., Western Jubilee Record Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Schroeder's Playboys... Walter Noble, fiddle; John Schroeder, guitar; Jerry Jacka, accordion; Tony Cordasco, bass... Square dance without calls... End of the world -- Sunflower square --; SWF 81.3/D.(78).807 (10in.)
- Arriba Lopez Portillo, Valenzuela, Gilberto, 1976; 1 sound disc, analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Gilberto Valenzuela... Arriba Lopez Portillo --; SWF 84.4/D.1 (7in.)
- The Liar's hour, Moore, Bill and Travis Edmonson, Cortaro, AZ., Latigo Records; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by Bill Moore and Travis Edmonson... The Liar's hour... The Liar's hour -- Sieery Petes -- Rye whiskey -- Boastful Bill -- The Dude wrangler -- High chin Bob -- Ole Red -- Hell in Texas -- La Vaquilla Colorado -- The Bronco with wings -- The Cowboy and the shepherd -- Judgement day -- Little Joe, the wrangler -- Ghost Canyon trail -- Yavapai Pete -- Lopin along -- Real cowboy life -- Ridge runnin' roan -- The Old nighthawk -- Ride around --; SWF 84.14/D.1 (12in.)
- Orpheus at Christmas, Orpheus and the Phoenix Boys Chorus, Phoenix, AZ; 1 sound disc, analog, [33 1/3 rpm], 12 in.; Performed by the Orpheus Male Chorus of Phoenix and the Phoenix Boys Chorus... Ralph Hess, director... Zoe Beeaff, accompaniest... The Cowboy's Christmas prayer (Narrator - R.D. McGill) -- Caroling, caroling -- The Christmas song (Solo - Neal W. Nielsen) -- Silver bells -- I'll be home for Christmas (Solo - Joseph Dodd) -- Sweet little Jesus boy (Solo - Clarence J. Davis; Harp - Susan Cochran) -- Echo carol (Phoenix Boys Chorus) -- O come all ye faithful (Phoenix Boys Chorus) -- Silent night -- Break forth, o beauteous heavenly light -- O bone Jesu -- Angels we have heard on high (Boys Chorus and Orpheus combined) --; SWF 84.14/D.2 (12in.)
- El Corrido de la huelga -- Por un amor, Lopez, Marta con Mariachi y Guitarras, Lopez Records; 1 sound disc (6 min.), analog, 45 rpm, 7 in.; Performed by Marta Lopez con Mariachi y Guitarras... Ranchera... El Corrido de la huelga (lyrics by Marta Lopez) -- Por un amor --; SWF 84.26/D.1 (7in.)
- [Folk music - Mexico. Selections], Martin y Malena con Mariachi, Peerless [April 7, 1921]; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Performed by Martin y Malena con Mariachi... Corrido... Primero Guanajuato (J. Arellano) -- Corrido de Cananea --; SWF 86.33/D.1 (10in.)
- [Folk music - Mexico. Selections], Los Montaneses del Alamo, Mexico, Discos Columbia de Mexico; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Performed by Los Montaneses del Alamo... Cantan Jaime y Nicando Mier... El Bracero vengador (corrido) -- Sueno ideal (ranchera) --; SWF 86.33/D.1 (10in.)
- [Folk music - Mexico. Selections], Trio Imperial, Los Angeles, CA., Imperial Record Co., 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Music by Trio Imperial... Corrido... Maldita suerte del pachuco (J. Rodriguez) -- El Borrachito (Lalo Guerrero) --; SWF 86.33/D.1 (10in.)
- [Folk music - Mexico. Selections], Los Madrugadores con Los Costenos, Mexico, Discos Columbia de Mexico; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Side 1: Performed by Los Madrugadores con Los Costenos... Amor y odio -- Side 2: Performed by Hermanos Quintero con los Charros de Atotonilcro... Soldado raso --; SWF 86.33/D.1 (10in.)
- [Folk music - Mexico. Selections], Los Madrugadores, Columbia; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Performed by Los Madrugadores - Hermanos Sanchez y Linares con guitarras... Corrido de Joaquin Murrieta - parts 1 and 2 --; SWF 86.33/D.1 (10in.)
- [Folk music - Mexico. Selections], Yaqui of Tlaxcala, Puebla, Camden, N.J., RCA Victor, copyright by L.C. Boulton; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; [Indian Music of Mexico]; Performed by Yaqui of Tlaxcala, Puebla... Recorded by Laura Boulton... Deer dance (Notched sticks, rattles, water drum, and singer) -- Pascolas (Harp, fiddle, bells, rattles, water drum and singer) --; SWF 86.33/D.1 (10in.)
- [Folk music - Mexico. Selections], Yaqui of Tlaxcala, Puebla, Camden, N.J., RCA Victor, copyright by L.C. Boulton; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; [Indian Music of Mexico]; Performed by Yaqui of Tlaxcala, Puebla... Recorded by Laura Boulton... Deer dance (Notched sticks, rattles, water drum, dog and singer) -- Pascolas (Flute, drum and bells) --; SWF 86.33/D.1 (10in.)
- [Folk music - Mexico. Selections], Yaqui of Tlaxcala, Puebla, Camden, N.J., RCA Victor, copyright by L.C. Boulton; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; [Indian Music of Mexico]; Performed by Yaqui of Tlaxcala, Puebla... Recorded by Laura Boulton... Pascolas (Flute and drum) -- Matachines (Harp, fiddle and stamping) --; SWF 86.33/D.1 (10in.)
- [Folk music - Mexico. Selections], Otomi of Honey, Puebla and Zapotec of Teotitlan, Oaxaca, Camden, N.J., RCA Victor, copyright by L.C. Boulton; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; [Indian Music of Mexico]; Recorded by Laura Boulton... Side 1: Performed by Otomi of Honey, Puebla... Flying pole dance (flute, drum, rattle) -- Performed by Zapotec of Teotitlan, Oaxaca... Fireworks music (chirimia and drum) --; SWF 86.33/D.1 (10in.)
- [Folk music - Mexico. Selections], Cuarteto Don Ramon, Sr., Los Angeles, CA., Taxco Recording Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Performed by Don Ramon, Sr. Cuarteto... Pachuco boogie (boogie) -- Guisa gacha (Guaracha) --; SWF 86.33/D.1 (10in.)
- [Folk music - Mexico. Selections], Hermandez y Jimenez con Guitarras, Los Angeles, CA., Acapulco Recording Co.; 1 sound disc, analog, 78 rpm, 10 in.; Performed by Hermandez y Jimenez con guitarras... El Bastardo (cancion) -- El corrido de angel de serna (David Jimenez)(corrido) --; SWF 86.33/D.1 (10in.)
- Navajo gift songs and round dance songs, 1971; Taos, N.M., Indian House, 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Navajo gift songs and round dance songs performed by singers: Boniface Bonnie, Autisdy Smith, M.D. Johnson, Roy Bonnie, Ben J. Johnson, Ted Bonnie, Benny Roanhorse, Donald Deal, Bertha Bonnie, Stella Bonnie, Winnie Bonnie, Nellie Curley, and Mary Deal... Recorded at Klagetoh, Ariz., March 16, 1968... Part of Enemy way ceremony...; SWF 87.12/D.1 (12in.)
- Navajo songs about love: Volume 1, The Klagetoh Swingers, 1976; Taos, N.M., Indian House, 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by The Klagetoh Swingers... Singers: Amos Y. Begay, Frank J. Begay, Ted B. Bonnie, Ned T. Clark, Ben J. Johnson, Joe J. Roanhorse... Recorded at Klagetoh, Ariz., Nov. 17, 1974... Modern style social dance songs performed at Navajo enemy way ceremonies during summmer...; SWF 87.12/D.2 (12in.)
- Navajo songs about love: Volume 2, The Klagetoh Swingers, 1976; Taos, N.M., Indian House, 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Performed by The Klagetoh Swingers... Singers: Amos Y. Begay, Frank J. Begay, Ted B. Bonnie, Ned T. Clark, Ben J. Johnson, Joe J. Roanhorse... Recorded at Klagetoh, Ariz., Nov. 17, 1974... Modern style social dance songs performed at Navajo enemy way ceremonies during summmer...; SWF 87.12/D.3 (12in.)
- Navajo songs about love: Volume 3, The Klagetoh Swingers, 1978; Taos, N.M., Indian House, 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Recorded at Klagetoh, Ariz., Nov. 13, 1977... Performed by The Klagetoh Swingers: Frank J. Begay, Ted B. Bonnie, Ned T. Clark, Robert P. Roan... Spin dance songs, skip dance songs, two-step songs...; SWF 87.12/D.4 (12in.)
- Navajo songs about love: Volume 4, The Klagetoh Swingers, 1978; Taos, N.M., Indian House, 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Recorded at Klagetoh, Ariz., Nov. 13, 1977...Performed by the Klagetoh Swingers: Frank J. Begay, Ted B. Bonnie, Ned T. Clark, Robert P. Roan... Two step songs...; SWF 87.12/D.5 (12in.)
- [Folk music. Selections], Klagetoh Maiden Singers, 1975; Taos, N.M., Indian House, 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Recorded at Klagetoh, Ariz., April 21, 1974.. Social songs from the Enemy Way ceremony or squaw dance... Klagetoh Maiden Singers: Jocetta Bonnie, Rose M. Bonnie, Winnie Bonnie, Marie E. Brown, and Bertha Johnson... Spin dance songs, walking dance songs, round dance songs, two step songs...; SWF 87.12/D.6 (12in.)
- Midnight sweetheart and other squaw dance songs, Bita Hochee Travelers, 1977; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1977; 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Recorded by Raymond Boley, Apr. 1977... Performers include Ned B. Morris, Lee Begay, Sam Begay, Larry Geshie... Squaw dance songs...; SWF 87.12/D.7 (12in.)
- Navajo squaw dance songs, Navajo Centennial Dance Team, 1970; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, 1 sound disc, analog, 33 1/3 rpm, 12 in.; Navajo Centennial Dance Team... Singers include: Alfred Yazzie, leader; Wilson Dahozy, Walter Yazzie, William Wilson, Arthur Newman, and Mark Slickey... Preamble to round dances -- round dances -- warm up songs -- courting songs -- escort songs -- skip dance songs -- quitting songs --; SWF 87.12/D.8 (12in.)